export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Well done for getting started! What would you like us to call you?",
    options: ["Toronto", "Vancouver", "Ottawa", "Montreal"],
    answer: "Ottawa",
  },
  {
    question: "Select your gender?" ,
    options: ["Venus", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
    answer: "Mars",
  },
  {
    question: "Which year are you born in?" ,
    options: ["Venus", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
    answer: "Mars",
  },
  {
    question: "What year are you currently in at university?",
    options: [
      "Charles Dickens",
      "William Shakespeare",
      "Jane Austen",
      "Mark Twain",
    ],
    answer: "William Shakespeare",
  },
  {
    question: "On average, how many hours do you sleep per night?",
    options: [
      "Atlantic Ocean",
      "Indian Ocean",
      "Arctic Ocean",
      "Pacific Ocean",
    ],
    answer: "Pacific Ocean",
  },
  {
    question: "On a typical day, how many hours do you spend studying?",
    options: ["Ag", "Au", "Fe", "Pb"],
    answer: "Au",
  },
  {
    question: "On a typical day, how many hours do you spend on screens for non-study activities (e.g., social media, gaming, TV) ?",
    options: ["Neil Armstrong", "Buzz Aldrin", "Yuri Gagarin", "John Glenn"],
    answer: "Neil Armstrong",
  },
  {
    question: "How many caffeinated drinks do you have per day(coffee, tea, energy drinks) ?",
    options: ["China", "Japan", "South Korea", "Thailand"],
    answer: "Japan",
  },
  {
    question: "How many minutes of vigorous physical activity do you do per day?",
    options: ["Gold", "Diamond", "Iron", "Quartz"],
    answer: "Diamond",
  },
  {
    question: "How would you rate your sleep quality on a scale of 1 to 10? (1 = Very poor, 10 = Excellent)",
    options: ["Gold", "Diamond", "Iron", "Quartz"],
    answer: "Diamond",
  },
  {
    question: "On weekdays, what time do you usually go to sleep? (24-hour format, e.g., 23:00 for 11 PM)",
    options: ["Africa", "Asia", "Europe", "South America"],
    answer: "Africa",
  },
  {
    question: "On weekends, what time do you usually go to sleep? (24-hour format, e.g., 00:30 for 12:30 AM)",
    options: [
      "Amazon River",
      "Nile River",
      "Yangtze River",
      "Mississippi River",
    ],
    answer: "Nile River",
  },
  {
    question: "On weekdays, what time do you usually wake up? (24-hour format, e.g., 07:00 for 7 AM)",
    options: [
      "Amazon River",
      "Nile River",
      "Yangtze River",
      "Mississippi River",
    ],
    answer: "Nile River",
  },
  {
    question: "On weekends, what time do you usually wake up? (24-hour format, e.g., 09:30 for 9:30 AM)",
    options: [
      "Amazon River",
      "Nile River",
      "Yangtze River",
      "Mississippi River",
    ],
    answer: "Nile River",
  },

];
